

I design for user experiences



+44 78 7816 5755



rodolfobiazi@icloud.com



https://rodolfo.work



in linkedin.com/in/rodolfodiniz

Profile

Designs interfaces, systems and products within the framing of human behavior. Enthusiastic designer with 4+ years of experience and specialization in iOS app development. Seeking to help generate forward-thinking, creative solutions and to deliver digital experience excellence.

Achievements

WWDC Swift Student Challenge | 2020

WWDC Student Scholarship | 2019

Education

Bachelor of Design 2017 - 2021

Pontifical Catholic University of Paraná

2012 - 2017 **Bachelor of Laws**

Pontifical Catholic University of Paraná

Skills

User Research **UX Prototyping** Systems Thinking Front-End Development Branding

Experience

Jr. Mentor 2021 - Present

Apple Developer Academy

Provided appropriate feedback and ensured every student received a positive collaborative experience in which they can learn and teach mutually.

Soft Skills

Problem Solving Public Speaking Leadership

2020 - 2021 **Lead Designer**

Cluster

Ensured the successful delivery of the app on both iOS and Android platforms. Produced and maintained the internal style guide while implementing new features based on user stories.

Language

English Portuguese

Intern/Student

Apple Developer Academy

Learned how to apply the CBL methodology in order to solve real-world challenges by working with students from different undergraduate degrees.

Reference

Fabio Binder Cordinator at Apple Academy fbinder@gmail.com

Joel Davies Apple Academy Team at Apple joel_davies@apple.com

2019 - 2020